
const questionArray = [
    {
        question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
        correct: "<script>",
        answers: [
            "<script>",
            "<soursce>",
            "<javascript>",
            "<js>"],
    },
    {
        question: "Which was the first browser to support JavaScript?",
        correct: "Netscape",
        answers: [
            "Mozilla Firefox",
            "Netscape",
            "Google Chrome",
            "IE"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the syntax for creating a function in JavaScript named as Geekfunc?",
        correct: "function Geekfunc()",
        answers: [
            "function = Geekfunc()",
            "function Geekfunc()",
            "function := Geekfunc()",
            "function : Geekfunc()"]
    },
    {
        question: " What method in JS removes the whitespace at the beginning and end of any string?",
        correct: "trim()",
        answers: [
            "strip()",
            "trim()",
            "stripped()",
            "trimmed()"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
        correct: "charAt()",
        answers: [
            "characterAt()",
            "getCharAt()",
            "charAt()",
            "None of the above."]
    },
    {
        question: "Which method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location?",
        correct: "substr()",
        answers: [
            "substr()",
            "getSubstring()",
            "slice()",
            "None of the above.",]
    },
    {
        question: "Which function of Number object returns the number's value?",
        correct: "valueOf()",
        answers: [
            "toString()",
            "valueOf()",
            "toLocaleString()",
            "toPrecision()",]
    },
    {
        question: "Which function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
        correct: "toLowerCase()",
        answers: [
            "toLocaleLowerCase()",
            "toLowerCase()",
            "toString()",
            "substring()",]
    },
    {
        question: "Which function of Array removes the last element from an array and returns it?",
        correct: "pop()",
        answers: [
            "pop()",
            "push()",
            "join()",
            "map()",]
    },
    {
        question: "Which function of Array removes the first element from an array and returns it?",
        correct: "shift()",
        answers: [
            "reverse()",
            "some()",
            "slice()",
            "shift()",]
    }
]